Finding Aid for the Fremont Ackerman Papers LSC.0312
UCLA Library Special Collections
Fremont Ackerman papers
1890-1945
UCLA Library Special Collections
Ackerman, Fremont
LSC.0312
1 unknown (62 boxes and 4 oversize boxes)
Fremont Ackerman worked as an engineer for the Northern Pacific Railroad Company in Montana. He later established his own business as a civil engineer and surveyor in the Southern California area. The collection consists of field books, maps, drawings, correspondence, and business papers related to Fremont Ackerman's work with the construction of the Northern Pacific Railroad in Montana and his activities as a civil engineer and surveyor in the Los Angeles region.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of William Coit Ackerman and Ruth Lovilla Ackerman, 1955.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 994621293606533
Biography
Ackerman graduated from Ohio State University in 1883; worked as an engineer for the Northern Pacific Railroad Company in Montana; moved to Los Angeles, California, and established his own business as a civil engineer and surveyor in the Southern California area.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of field books, maps, drawings, correspondence, and business papers related to engineer Fremont Ackerman. Materials relate to his work with the construction of the Northern Pacific Railroad in Montana and his activities as a civil engineer and surveyor in the Los Angeles region. Topics include land and water companies in Arizona and California and real estate development in Southern California. Includes surveys conducted by Ackerman for the Lucky Baldwin estate, William Wolfskill rancho, Abbot Kinney's Venice in America project, and the property of William Andrews Clark.
Land surveys.; Drawings.; Real estate development -- California, Southern.; Surveyors -- California, Southern -- Archives.; Civil engineers -- California -- Los Angeles -- Archives.; Railroad engineers -- Montana -- Archives.; Northern Pacific Railroad Company; Ackerman, Fremont--Archives.
- Surveys. (Box 1)
- Rolled blueprints & survey material. (Box 2)
- Correspondence. (Box 3)
- Maps published by oil companies, etc., some correspondence. (Box 4)
- The Oil Fields of Southern California. Federal Writers Project, typescript (carbon) with notations. 1 vol. with surveys, etc. of Wolfskill Ranch, 1936. (Box 5)
- Envelope with clippings of C. Cole articles sent to the Los Angeles Herald, one envelope of correspondence. (Box 6)
- Miscellaneous surveys. (Box 7, Box 8, Box 9)
- Bank records (cancelled checks, etc.). 19 vol. of daily accounts, ca., 1905-1908. (Box 10)
- Bank records, file of patent papers. (Box 11)
- Bank records, tax receipts. (Box 12)
- Correspondence. (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous surveys, correspondence. (Box 14)
- Surveys, 10 envelopes of tax receipts. (Box 15)
- Correspondence, memo book on Pasadena account, publications on taxes, wills & estates. (Box 16)
- Correspondence. (Box 17)
- Survey notes & reports. (Box 18, Box 19)
- Los Angeles City Civilian Defense report, historical records survey, manual of instructions for indexes., December 1, 1941 (Box 20)
- Survey reports [insect damaged]. (Box 21)
- Account ledger, business cards, survey figures and notes, empty envelopes. (Box 22)
- Survey notes, correspondence, receipts, financial records. (Box 23)
- Survey notes, receipts, bank records, La Fiesta de Los Angeles envelopes. (Box 24)
- Bank records, receipts, survey notes. (Box 25)
- Survey notebooks, school notebooks, memoranda books [all insect damaged], 1883. (Box 26)
- Index no.3 maps [Finding Aid inventory], oil company reports, survey notes. (Box 27)
- Survey notes, laws & regulations, oil company correspondence, bank statements. (Box 28)
- Index to field books, papers re field books. (Box 29)
- Field books 18-37. (Box 30)
- Field books 38-60. (Box 31)
- Field books 61-75. (Box 32)
- Survey notes, bank statements & receipts. (Box 33)
- Real estate law, legal blanks, city specifications, bills & receipts. (Box 34)
- Bank statements & receipts. (Box 35)
- Bank statements & receipts, business correspondence, receipts. (Box 36)
- Ledgers, 1902-1910. (Box 37)
- Ledgers, 1902-1922. (Box 38)
- Personal expense books, 1911-1928. (Box 39)
- Ledgers, 1932-1939. (Box 40)
- Correspondence. (Box 41)
- Bank statements, oil company receipts. (Box 42)
- Surveys - A. (Box 43)
- Surveys - B. (Box 44, Box 45)
- Surveys - C. (Box 46, Box 47)
- Surveys - D. (Box 48)
- Surveys - E & F. (Box 49)
- Surveys - G. (Box 50)
- Surveys - H. (Box 51, Box 52)
- Surveys - I through K. (Box 53)
- Surveys - L. (Box 54)
- Surveys - M. (Box 55)
- Surveys - R. (Box 56)
- Surveys - S. (Box 57, Box 58)
- Surveys - T. (Box 59)
- Surveys, miscellaneous & unsorted. (Box 60, Box 61, Box 62)
- Ledger, 1894-1986. (Box 63)
- Ledger, 2 vol., 1906. (Box 64)
- 119th Place Profile--Budlong Avenue & Vermont Avenue, Los Angeles., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 132)
- 132nd Street & 133rd Street profile--Hoover Street to Vermont Avenue, Los Angeles., 1930.; 1 item. (Box 132)
- 135th Street--Hoover Street to Vermont Avenue, Los Angeles., 1930.; 1 item. (Box 132)
- Ackerman & Lanterman Survey--map--North of Playa del Rey, La Ballona Ranch, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 115)
- Ackerman (Fremont)--certificate of commission as licensed land survey--state of California, Los Angeles., 1903.; 1 item. (Box 154)
- Ackerman (Fremont)--personal & business papers and photograph of road construction. ca. Los Angeles., 1903-1941.; 50 items. (Box 155)
- Ackerman (Fremont) home--1011 W. 23rd Street, Los Angeles., n.d.; 75 items. (Box 106)
- Ackerman (Fremont) home--539 S. Serrano, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 10 items. (Box 107)
- Ahearn Block--Budlong Avenue & 38th St., Los Angeles County., 1898.; 1 item. (Box 114)
- Ahearn Tract subdivision--Kansas Street & 38th St., Los Angeles County., 1898.; 2 items. (Box 114)
- Alamitos Bay Tract, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 153)
- Alhambra Tract--S.W. Champion Survey--Granada Avenue & Alhambra Street, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 117)
- Aliso Avenue, Los Angeles., 1910.; 1 item. (Box 69)
- Allegheny Street--Soto Street to Dacotah Street, Los Angeles., 1924.; 1 item. (Box 130)
- Alosta Street--Soto Street to Dacotah Street, Los Angeles., 1924.; 1 item. (Box 107)
- Alpine--Soledad Canyon--Southern Pacific Railroad, California., 1929.; 3 items. (Box 136)
- Alpine Mining Claims, Los Angeles County., 1929.; 1 item. (Box 139)
- Andrews Boulevard / First Street, Los Angeles., 1908.; 3 items. (Box 65)
- Annandale Vista--Ave. Sixty-Four / Nithsdale Street, Los Angeles County., 1928.; 5 items. (Box 84)
- Arizona--Topographic Map, Arizona., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 149)
- Arlington Heights Terrace, Los Angeles., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 156)
- Arlington Heights Terrace--Washington Street & Francisquito Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1906.; 7 items. (Box 112)
- Arlington Heights Tract--Subdivision no.1 (Harry Jackins), Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Arlington Heights Tract no.2 (Jarry Jackins), Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Arlington Street / Santa Monica Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1909.; 1 item. (Box 67)
- Asbury Tract--Cypress Avenue & Elm Street, Los Angeles., 1908.; 3 items. (Box 113)
- Ascot South Park Tract--Strong & Dickinson, Los Angeles County., 1905.; 5 items. (Box 108)
- Athens, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 70)
- Athens--128th Street / Hoover Street 1921. Los Angeles County., 1 item. (Box 79)
- Athens on the Hill, Los Angeles., n.d.; 4 items. (Box 153)
- Athens on the Hill (folder 1 of 3), Los Angeles County., 1905-1913.; 69 items. (Box 91)
- Athens on the Hill (folder 2 of 3), Los Angeles County., 1905-1913.; 34 items. (Box 92)
- Athens on the Hill (folder 3 of 3), Los Angeles County., 1905-1913.; 34 items. (Box 93)
- Avenue Forty / Scandia Way, Los Angeles., 1923.; 3 items. (Box 80)
- Babcock (A.R.) Tract--Scott Street & Viola Street, Los Angeles., 1906.; 3 items. (Box 115)
- Ballona & South Santa Monica Road, Los Angeles., 1899.; 1 item. (Box 132)
- Baroness Tract--Boundary Avenue & Roberta Street, Los Angeles., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 128)
- Bassett Survey--Hill Street & Clay Street, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 121)
- Baugh Road--Baugh Tract in Rancho San Rafael, n.p., 1899.; 1 item. (Box 132)
- Beachwood Park--Franklin Avenue & Beachwood Dr, Los Angeles., 1910.; 1 item. (Box 115)
- Beaumont, Riverside County., 1 item. (Box 156)
- Bentley Avenue, Los Angeles., 1938.; 1 item. (Box 80)
- Bernard Avenue & Campbell Avenue, n.p., 1887.; 1 item. (Box 129)
- Beverly (City of), Los Angeles County., 1914.; 1 item. (Box 75)
- Bonita Place--San Fernando Road & Bonita Dr, Los Angeles County., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 114)
- Boulder County, Colorado, Colorado., 1902.; 1 item. (Box 149)
- Bowen and Chamberlins Main & Figueroa Street Tract no.2, Los Angeles., 1930.; 1 item. (Box 107)
- Boyle Avenue--7th Street to 9th Street, Los Angeles., 1924.; 2 items. (Box 130)
- Brandt Tract--Morningside Avenue & San Gabriel Boulevard Pasadena., 1927.; 3 items. (Box 107)
- Brentwood Park (Map of), Los Angeles., 1930.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Briarcliff Road, Los Angeles., 1936.; 3 items. (Box 81)
- Bridgedale Acres--Strawberry Street & Cypress Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1910.; 5 items. (Box 118)
- Briggs Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1914.; 2 items. (Box 75)
- Brockley's Acre Lots--Vermont Avenue / Washington Street, Los Angeles., n.d.; 4 items. (Box 156)
- Burbank--Western portion, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 148)
- Butler's South West Tract--Santa Monica Avenue & Western Avenue, Los Angeles., 1903.; 1 item. (Box 125)
- California & Nevada map and presidential wall atlas (on verso), >n.p., 1 item. (Box 153)
- California motor route map--Los Angeles and Approaches--published by Security First National Bank, Southern California., 1 item. (Box 153)
- Call (J.H.)--Survey for--boundary line, Los Angeles County., 1911.; 2 items. (Box 108)
- Calo Tract--Fifth Street & San Pedro Street, Los Angeles County., 1925.; 4 items. (Box 120)
- Carrizosa Tract--Alameda Street & 55th Street, Los Angeles., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 118)
- Carson Street / Hoover Street, Los Angeles County., 1920.; 4 items. (Box 79)
- Carver Place--Part of Highland View tract--Washington Dr.& Marmion, Los Angeles County., 1913.; 2 items. (Box 111)
- Castle Hills Subdivision--Los Amigos Street, Los Angeles County., 1939.; 6 items. (Box 125)
- Central Avenue / Albert Street, Los Angeles County., 1914.; 4 items. (Box 75)
- Central Avenue / Main Street, Los Angeles County., 1918.; 1 item. (Box 77)
- Central Park Tract (Strong & Dickinson)--Central Avenue & 49th Street, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 2 items. (Box 117)
- Central Park Tract (Strong & Dickinson)--Central Avenue / 50th Street, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Cerritos Avenue, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 75)
- Chamberlin's Central Avenue Tract--Central Avenue & Hooper Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1906.; 2 items. (Box 124)
- Chapman (John S.)--4th Avenue, Los Angeles., 1940.; 1 item. (Box 125)
- Chapman Ranch--F.E. Edwards land--Foothill Boulevard & Walnut Avenue, Los Angeles., 1914.; 3 items. (Box 108)
- Chenault Street, Los Angeles County., 1925.; 1 item. (Box 84)
- Chino Ranch, San Bernardino County., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 136)
- Clark & Bryan Tract--San Pedro Street, Los Angeles., 1924.; 1 item. (Box 124)
- Clawson Villa Tract--Vermont Avenue & 48th Street, Los Angeles., 1904.; 3 items. (Box 109)
- Cleeves (Dr. Montague)--Licensed Surveyor's Map, Los Angeles County., 1928.; 1 item. (Box 121)
- Clement Tract--Anderson Street & 2nd Street, Los Angeles., 1939.; 2 items. (Box 121)
- Coburn Park, Los Angeles County., 1923.; 1 item. (Box 82)
- Coffman Partition--Coffman and Pico Road & Whittier Road, Montebello, California., 1911.; 1 item. (Box 127)
- Cohn's Partition, Los Angeles County., 1921-1935.; 12 items. (Box 105)
- Cohn's Partition--Mill Road, Los Angeles., 1895, 1921, 1924.; 3 items. (Box 127)
- Colina Park, Los Angeles County., 1922.; 1 item. (Box 107)
- Colorado Street / Monte Vista Avenue, Pasadena., 1923.; 23 items. (Box 83)
- Colorado Street / Valley Dr, 1908.; 3 items. (Box 66)
- Commonwealth Avenue 1st Street to 3rd Street, Los Angeles., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 132)
- Commonwealth Avenue / Third Street, Los Angeles County., 1908.; 6 items. (Box 68)
- Compton Avenue Tract (Strong & Dickinson)--Compton Avenue & 25th Street, Los Angeles., 1903.; 3 items. (Box 116)
- Concrete Arch Bridge, Sante Fe, New Mexico., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 137)
- Cordit Tract--Santa Monica Avenue & Normandie Avenue, Los Angeles., 1905.; 1 item. (Box 117)
- Cornish, Easton & Holmes Tract--Myrtle Street & First Street, Los Angeles County., 1910.; 1 item. (Box 117)
- Cottage Terrace--Elm Street & San Fernando Road, Los Angeles County., 1906.; 5 items. (Box 114)
- Country Club Park--9th Street & Street Andrews Place, Los Angeles., 1 item. (Box 128)
- Country Club Park--Subdivision no.1, Los Angeles., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 156)
- Country Club Park--Subdivision no.2, Los Angeles., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 156)
- Country Club Park--Western Avenue & 9th Street, Los Angeles County., 1905.; 1 item. (Box 125)
- County form for filing maps, Los Angeles County., 1916.; 1 item. (Box 148)
- County Rd.--Rose Hill to South Pasadena, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 130)
- Crestmont--Carnation Avenue & Landa Street, Los Angeles., 1923.; 9 items. (Box 119)
- Cribb & Sinclairs's Subdivision--Normandie Avenue & 21st Street, Los Angeles., 1904.; 2 items. (Box 125)
- Cribb & Street Clair Lot (Mott Tract)--4th Street & Hope Street, Los Angeles., 1907.; 3 items. (Box 114)
- Cripple Creek Mining District (New Map of)--El Paso County, Colorado., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 149)
- Cucamonga Town Site--Milliken Avenue at New Arrow Boulevard Cucamonga, California., 1932.; 1 item. (Box 140)
- Culver's East Hollywood Tract--Vermont Avenue & Lexington Avenue, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 128)
- Cummings (Dr.)--Portions of tracts 3369, 2099, and Lick Tract, Los Angeles County., 1929.; 1 item. (Box 120)
- Cummings (Dr.) / Linwood Dr, Los Angeles County., 1930.; 8 items. (Box 82)
- Cummings (Dr.) / Linwood Dr, Los Angeles County., 1930.; 10 items. (Box 84)
- Cummings (W.E.) and Cecil B. DeMille Road, Los Angeles., 1919.; 1 item. (Box 133)
- Cummings (W.E.) and Fraters (J.A.), Los Angeles County., 1928.; 2 items. (Box 139)
- Cummings (W.E.) property--Franklin Avenue & Normandie Avenue, Hollywood., 1923.; 1 item. (Box 120)
- Cunningham Tract--Hope Street & Laurel Street, Los Angeles., 1887.; 2 items. (Box 128)
- Curry Tract--South Park Avenue & 45th Street, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 116)
- Curry Tract on South Park Avenue (Goodenow & McClung), Long Beach (?)., n.d.; 3 items. (Box 156)
- Dacotah Street--9th Street to Alosta Street, Los Angeles., 1924.; 1 item. (Box 133)
- Dacotah Street--9th Street to Hollenbeck Avenue, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 130)
- Daisy Street profile--Morningside Avenue to Blanche Street, Pasadena., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 133)
- De Luckhardt (Pillar A.)--Soto Street & Southern California Railway (?), Los Angeles., 1925.; 1 item. (Box 120)
- DeMille (Cecil B.)--Hunter Ranch, Los Angeles County., 1930.; 4 items. (Box 126)
- DeMille (Cecil B.)--Paradise Ranch--Little Tujunga Road, Los Angeles County., 1928, 1930, 1934.; 4 items. (Box 126)
- Denver map issued by United States National Bank, Denver., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Denver Northwestern & Pacific Railway (Map of the)--projected lines Denver to Salt Lake City, Colorado., 1902.; 1 item. (Box 149)
- Denver Northwestern Pacific Railway, Denver to Salt Lake City., 1902.; 4 items. (Box 138)
- Dodge Ranch--Rancho Santa Anita Avenue--White Oak Avenue & Walnut Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1908.; 1 item. (Box 116)
- Dolgeville, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 153)
- Downey & Florence Rd. Flood Control Map, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 138)
- Dye (Helen) tract--map of Figueroa Street & First Street, Los Angeles County., 1903.; 1 item. (Box 110)
- East Jefferson Street Tract, Long Beach., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Echo Park Road Tract, Los Angeles., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 139)
- Echo Park Road Tract--Effie Street & Echo Park Road, Los Angeles., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 117)
- Edenhurst Avenue / Parkdale Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1922.; 1 item. (Box 81)
- Edwards (Frank E.) property located at Chapman Station, Los Angeles County., 1916-1917.; 1 item. (Box 137)
- Eldora, Colorado--Vicinity of, Colorado., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 149)
- Election returns, Los Angeles., 1928.; 1 item. (Box 148)
- Elysian Vista Scott Tract--Echo Park Road & Avalon Street, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 2 items. (Box 111)
- Emerald Bay, Orange County., October 1928.; 1 item. (Box 157)
- Emil Bloch's Seaport Tract--Strawberry Street, Los Angeles County., 1910.; 1 item. (Box 118)
- Engineering charts, plans, graphs, n.p., v.d.; 21 items. (Box 147)
- Etal (Claribel Doty) Property in Franklin County, Ohio, Franklin County, Ohio., 1928.; 1 item. (Box 139)
- Etiwanda Commercial Tract, Los Angeles County., 1932.; 1 item. (Box 139)
- Evergreen Avenue--9th Street to Hollenbeck Avenue, Los Angeles., 1924.; 1 item. (Box 130)
- Ezra Street--Hollenbeck Avenue to 9th Street, Los Angeles., 1926.; 1 item. (Box 134)
- Faucet Avenue / Pottrero, Los Angeles County., 1916.; 1 item. (Box 67)
- Fifth Avenue / Sixth Avenue, Los Angeles., 1920.; 5 items. (Box 78)
- Figueroa Square--Figueroa & 41st Street, Los Angeles County., 1905.; 4 items. (Box 125)
- Figueroa Street / Salon Avenue, Los Angeles., 1910.; 2 items. (Box 69)
- Figueroa Street Tract (Clark & Bryan)--Figueroa Street / Santa Monica Avenue, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Figueroa Street Tract (Strong & Dickinson), Los Angeles., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 156)
- Figueroa Street Tract--Strong & Dickinson, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 4 items. (Box 110)
- First & Broadway & San Gabriel Boulevard, East San Gabriel, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 139)
- First Street & E. San Gabriel Street, San Gabriel & Los Angeles County., 1907.; 1 item. (Box 134)
- First Street--Juanita Avenue to Vermont Avenue, Los Angeles., 1907.; 1 item. (Box 120)
- First Street / Broadway, Los Angeles., 1922.; 1 item. (Box 81)
- First Street Profile--Hoover Street to a point 2000 ft. west, Los Angeles., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 132)
- Fisher's Map of Los Nietos, Los Angeles County (?)., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 139)
- Florence Villa Tract--Alameda Street & Florence Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1905, 1922.; 5 items. (Box 123)
- Forest Park--Subdivisions 1 & 2--Commonwealth Ave & Third St., Virgil & Hoover, Los Angeles., 1906, 1907.; 17 items. (Box 122)
- Frank Sibichi Tract, Los Angeles., 1897.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Franklin Avenue & Edgmont, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 124)
- Franklin Avenue / Normandie, Los Angeles County., 1919, 1928.; 10 items. (Box 77)
- Franklin Street, Los Angeles County., 1919.; 1 item. (Box 74)
- Freeways (master plan), Los Angeles., 1947.; 3 items. (Box 156)
- Fruit Acres Tract--Compton Avenue / 64th Street, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Ganesha Park Tract--Huntington Boulevard & Orange Grove Avenue, Pasadena., 1908.; 5 items. (Box 119)
- Garfield Heights Tract (Cribb & Sinclair)--Washington Street & Cimarron Street, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 123)
- Garfield Heights Tract (Cribb & Sinclair)--Washington Street & Hermosa Street, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Garvey School District Lot--part of Garvey Ranch, Los Angeles County., 1917.; 2 items. (Box 108)
- Geneva Street to 3rd Street--Alley, Los Angeles., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 131)
- Gilkerson Tract--Florence & Downey Road, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 123)
- Glassell Road, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 67)
- Glendora Acres, Los Angeles County., 1929-1944.; 14 items. (Box 85)
- Glendora Mountain View Addition--Minnesota Avenue & Whitcomb Avenue, Los Angeles., 1907.; 3 items. (Box 113)
- Glenn Avenue--Camulos Street to Ezra Street, Los Angeles., 1923.; 1 item. (Box 107)
- Glenn Avenue--Soto Street to Camulos Street, Los Angeles., 1924.; 1 item. (Box 129)
- Goetz Tract / Acres--Broadway & First Street, Los Angeles., 1919, 1922.; 2 items. (Box 123)
- Gower Street, Los Angeles County., 1916.; 5 items. (Box 75)
- Grand County, Colorado, Colorado., 1903.; 2 items. (Box 149)
- Grand View Heights--Western Avenue & 24th Street, Los Angeles., After 1915.; 1 item. (Box 128)
- Grand View Tract no.2 (George H. Peck's), San Pedro., 2 items. (Box 156)
- Grider & Orange Orangedale Tract, Los Angeles., 1896.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Gunn (Alexander) Tract--Downey Road, Los Angeles., 1906.; 3 items. (Box 121)
- Gunnison County, Colorado, Colorado., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 149)
- Hamilton (Mrs. L.M.)--survey of San Pedro property, Los Angeles County., 1906.; 2 items. (Box 137)
- Hampton Heights--Cypress Avenue & Idell Street, Los Angeles County., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 125)
- Hampton Terrace (Highland Park), Highland Park., 1905.; 2 items. (Box 156)
- Hannon Property--Compton Avenue & 20th Street, Los Angeles., 1926.; 1 item. (Box 120)
- Hannon Tract--28th Street & Compton Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1908.; 2 items. (Box 113)
- Harbor Boulevard--Palm Avenue & Harbor Boulevard Los Angeles County., 1911.; 1 item. (Box 130)
- Haskell Tract / Newcastle Avenue & Santa Rita Street, Los Angeles County., 1928.; 11 items. (Box 101)
- Heart of Los Angeles--Transportation map, Los Angeles., 1935.; 1 item. (Box 149)
- Highland / Wilson, Los Angeles., 1907.; 1 item. (Box 65)
- Highland Avenue, Los Angeles., 1916.; 1 item. (Box 75)
- Highland Park extension--Ave. 49 & Avenue 50, Los Angeles County., 1902.; 1 item. (Box 111)
- Highland Villa Tract--Brooklyn Avenue / Rowan Avenue, Los Angeles., 1 item. (Box 156)
- Hill Synd. Tract, Los Angeles., 1911.; 3 items. (Box 67)
- Hillhurst Park--Western Avenue & Gendower Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 113)
- Holbrook Avenue / Redman Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1923.; 1 item. (Box 82)
- Holcomb's Lorena Heights Homes, Los Angeles., n.d.; 3 items. (Box 67)
- Hollenbeck Avenue, Los Angeles., 1923.; 2 items. (Box 107)
- Hollenbeck Avenue & Soto Street, Los Angeles County., 1926.; 8 items. (Box 100)
- Hollenbeck Ranch--Ruddock Street & Lyman Street, Los Angeles., 1920.; 3 items. (Box 118)
- Holly Glen, Los Angeles., 1912.; 3 items. (Box 66)
- Hollywood Cemetery--Avenue plan, Hollywood, California., 1908.; 1 item. (Box 137)
- Hollywood District Map, Los Angeles., 1916.; 1 item. (Box 140)
- Hollywood Glen, Los Angeles County., 1910.; 5 items. (Box 68)
- Hollywood Ocean View Terrace, Los Angeles., 1910.; 4 items. (Box 69)
- Home Villa Tract / Twenty-second Place / Bronson Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1921.; 2 items. (Box 79)
- Honolulu--Territory of Hawaii, Hawaii., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 149)
- Hoover Street / First Street, Los Angeles County., 1921.; 1 item. (Box 80)
- Hoover Street--south of 1st Street, Los Angeles., 1909.; 1 item. (Box 131)
- Hoover Tract--Union Avenue & 23rd Street, Los Angeles., 1910-1913.; 2 items. (Box 129)
- Hostetter (folder 1 of 3), Los Angeles County., 1923. 1924.; 78 items. (Box 86)
- Hostetter (folder 2 of 3), Los Angeles County., 1923-1924.; 32 items. (Box 87)
- Hostetter (folder 3 of 3), Los Angeles County., 1923-1924.; 31 items. (Box 88)
- Hostetter Tract--Rio Vista, Soto, etc, Los Angeles., 1928.; 11 items. (Box 135)
- Howes Tract--35th Street & Denker Avenue, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 128)
- Hudson Street, Los Angeles County., 1927.; 2 items. (Box 82)
- Hunters Highland View Tract (plot)--Isabel Street & Loosmore Street, Los Angeles., 1920.; 1 item. (Box 118)
- Huntington Drive--Farmdale Avenue to Fairoaks Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1906.; 2 items. (Box 130)